



Summary

Experienced Graphic Designer and Web Developer with 5 years experience in professional print production settings and working with in-house design teams, artists, and manufacturers. Over 10 years experience working with the Adobe Creative Suite producing graphics and assets for businesses and individuals. Innovative thinker who has re-shaped work spaces improving quality of work and life.

Professional Experience

2019 - 21 Graphic Designer/Production Artist, Denial Print Company, Folsom PA

Developed graphic art and designs for clients for the purpose of garment and merchandise printing. Automated workflow to increase accuracy, quality, and efficiency of the in-house proM duction workflow. Revised the company's web presence by building web assets, social media templates, and advertisements. Generated online forms to improve the customer's experience and improve internal quality of life for the sales department.

Tasks: Prepress, Finishing, Quality Control, File Management, Product Finishing, Large Format Printing.

2018 Intern, Applied Image LLC, Freehold NJ

Produced large format and environmental graphics for clients including the National Aquarium in Baltimore, MD. Produced artwork for murals under the supervision of the graphic design team. Up-kept studio quality and performed general maintenance on printers and plotters Tasks: Pre-press, Finishing, Printing, Plotting, Weeding, Laminating, Studio Maintenance.

2016 - 18 Printer Technician, MICA, Baltimore MD

Managed the digital printing studio at the Printmaking Department facilities. Established the foundation of the department's risograph press by producing color charts and running workM shops for students. Educated students on fine art digital printing, screen printing, and best studio practices. Acted as a consultant in digital printing processes for visiting artists and the student body.

Tasks: Pre-press, Consultant, Educator, Hosted regularly scheduled workshops and office hours.

2014 - 18 Studio Assistant, Quentin Mosely, Jimmy Joe Roche, Baltimore MD

Designed and created custom 16mm film hardware for the short film Skin of Man. Printed cover art, inserts, and advertisement materials for the music label Ultra Violet Light. Assisted in conM structing a large public installation for the first annual Light City Baltimore.

Education

2021 2018	Full Stack Web and Mobile Development, Nucamp Coding Bootcamp BFA Printmaking Maryland Institute College of Art, Baltimore MD	
Skills	Languages & Software	Skills
	Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects,	Project Management, Customer Service, A/V
	Indesign, Premiere, Audition, Medium)	Production, Screen Printing, Large Format
	Spark AR, Rhinoceros, HTML, CSS/SCSS/Sass,	Printing
	Javascript, React, Redux	